lumapartners.com 2019-12-19

# Privacy & Cookies Policy | LUMA Partners

**Privacy Policy**

LUMA Partners LLC (“LUMA Partners”) takes precautions to maintain the privacy of nonpublic personal information concerning its current and prospective clients. These precautions include the adoption of certain procedures designed to maintain and secure such clients’ nonpublic personal information from inappropriate disclosure to third parties.

In connection with providing investment banking services, LUMA Partners may collect nonpublic personal information about its clients.

LUMA Partners does not disclose any nonpublic personal information about its prospective, existing or former clients to anyone, except as permitted by applicable law and regulation.

LUMA Partners restricts access to nonpublic personal information about its clients to those employees and agents of LUMA Partners who need to know that information in order to provide services to its clients.

LUMA Partners may disclose such information to its affiliates and to service providers and financial institutions that provide services to LUMA Partners.

LUMA Partners will require such third-party service providers and financial institutions to protect the confidentiality of clients’ nonpublic personal information and to use the information only for purposes for which it is disclosed to them. LUMA Partners maintains physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to safeguard clients’ nonpublic personal information and which LUMA Partners believes are adequate to prevent unauthorized disclosure of such information.

If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please contact Susan Marshall (646) 786-8423 at the office of LUMA Partners.

To give you the best possible experience, this site uses cookies. By viewing this site, you agree to our use of cookies. Should you need to find out more about the cookies we use, view our Cookies & Privacy Policy.Accept
